A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.31 (A2005) FA491
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2005.039: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2004; AC.2005.039; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3727, R3728, R3733, R3734
  - Health Equity (HE) - Areil Pablos-Mendez Trip and Meeting Files, AC.2005.039.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - September 27, 2000: Washington, DC - Microbicides Development Meeting, 2000 September 27 (Box R3733)
    - December 7-9, 2000: Oxfordshire, England - Intellectual Property Rights and Global Health, 2000 December 7-9 (Box R3733)
    - December 14, 2000: Washington, DC - Meeting of the Working Group 2 Core Membership on Macroeconomics, 2000 Deccember 14 (Box R3733)
    - January 2001: Trip to India, 2001 January (Box R3733)
    - June 10-12, 2001: Montreux, Switzerland - Global Vaccine Research Forum Meeting, 2001 June 10-12 (Box R3733)
    - June 24-29, 2001: New London, NH - Drug Development for TB, 2001 June 24-29 (Box R3733)
    - July 19-20, 2001: Washington, DC - Working Group 2/Commission Meeting, 2001 July 19-20 (Box R3733)
    - March 25-27, 2002: Havana, Cuba - Biotechnology and Genomics Meeting, 2002 March 25-27 (Box R3733)
    - May 2, 2002: Lenexa, Kansas -Felton International, 2002 May 2 (Box R3733)
    - July 3-10, 2002: Salzburg, Austria - Salzburg Seminar, 2002 July 3-10 (Box R3733)
    - October 12-14, 2002: Geneva, Switzerland - Social Entrepreneurs' Summit 2002, 2002 October 12-14 (Box R3733)
    - November 10-15, 2002: Arusha, Tanzania - Global Forum Meeting, 2002 November 10-15 (Box R3733)
    - May 28, 2003: Boston, MA - Human Resources Management Meeting at JFK School of Government, 2003 May 28 (Box R3733)
    - November 3-8, 2003: Geneva, Switzerland - WHO Meetings, 2003 November 3-8 (Box R3733)
    - December 8, 2003: London, England - Complexity Theory and Health Care, 2003 December 8 (Box R3733)
    - February 18-20, 2004: Washington, DC - Reaching the Poor, 2004 February 18-20 (Box R3733)
    - March 11-12, 15-16, 2004: Barcelona, Spain -Human Resources for Health and Development: JLI-WG Coordination Meeting, 2004 March 11-12 (Box R3733)
  - Health Equity (HE) - Timothy G. Evans Trip and Meeting Files, AC.2005.039.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - Access to Medicines (UK Working Group), 2001-2003 (Box R3734)
    - Beaglehole, Robert (visit to RF May 14-16, 2001) (Box R3734)
    - Emory University, 2003 March (Box R3734)
    - Essential Drugs, 2000-2002 (Box R3734)
    - Global Public Goods, 2002 January 15 (Box R3734)
    - IMMPACT (Initiative for Maternal Mortality Programme Assessment) Meeting at RF, 2001 February 6 (Box R3734)
    - Leadership in International Health Development, 1996-1997; 2000 (Box R3734)
    - Population - Foundation Leaders Meeting, 2001 January 9 (Box R3734)
    - Sinding, Steven W., 2000-2002 (Box R3734)
    - Strategic Planning (HE), 2000-2001 (Box R3734)
    - Strengthening Global Leadership (SGL) Working Group, 2000 (Box R3734)
    - Tuberculosis (TB) (#1), 2000 (Box R3734)
    - Tuberculosis (TB) (#2), 1998-1999 (Box R3734)
    - UNICEF -Meeting on Socio-economic disparities in health nutrition and education, 2002 October 2 (Box R3734)
    - United Nations - Strategic Planning Meeting of the Secretary General, 2002 January 11-12 (Box R3734)
    - World Bank, The, 1998-2003 (Box R3734)
    - World Health Organization (WHO, 1998-2002 (Box R3734)
- AC.2005.047: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1986-2004; AC.2005.047; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3729, R3730.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.047.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 96019 - CHILDREN'S VACCINE INITIATIVE, 1990-1999 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96020 #62 - FAMILY HEALTH INTERNATIONAL - INDUSTRIAL COLLABORATION IN CONTRACEPTIVE RESEARCH, 1996-2000 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96020 #67 - (POPULATION SCIENCES) - BC CONFERENCE: APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR PHARMACOLOGY FOR POST-TESTICULAR ACTIVITY, 1997-1999 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96022 #710 - SALLAR, ANTHONY MAWULI - ADIA: DETERMINANTS OF SEXUAL RISK TAKING OF ADOLESCENTS IN GHANA, 1997-2002 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96022 #758 - ANGIMA, SAMSON DANFORD - ADIA: ADAPTATION OF RUSLE MODEL IN KENYA, 1997-2000 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96022 #760 - WEGULO, FRANCIS N. - ACA: ENERGY AND DEVELOPMENT IN RURAL AREAS OF KENYA, 1996-2004 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96022 #779 - MUSENERO, MONICA JANE - ADIA: TUBERCULOSIS IN RURAL UGANDA, 1998-2004 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96029 #3 - (COMMISSION ON TEACHER TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT) - BC CONFERENCE: TEACHER DEVELOPMENT, 1996-1999 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96034 #113 - CHIANG MAI UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - "LIFE SKILLS TRAINING FOR YOUTH PROJECT", 1996-2003 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96040 #48 - OBOR, INC. - EDUCATIONAL BOOK PUBLICATION AND DISTRIBUTION IN KENYA, 1991-2001 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96041 #48 - JERUSALEM INSTITUTE FOR ISRAEL STUDIES (ISRAEL) - RESEARCH PROJECT ON "IMAGE OF THE OTHER", 1996-2004 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96041 #49 - INTERNATIONAL PEACE AND COOPERATION CENTER (ISRAEL) - MUTUAL PERCEPTIONS OF JEWS AND MUSLIMS, 1997-2001 (Box R3729)
    - RF 96047 #102 - FREGOSO-TIRADO, LUIS E. - FORAGE PRODUCTION SYSTEMS AND SOIL QUALITY IN SOUTH SINALOA, MEXICO, 1996-2002 (Box R3730)
    - RF 96047 #113 - NETWORK FOR STUDIES ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT (MEXICO) - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT IN MEXICO, 1997-2001 (Box R3730)
    - RF 96047 #114 - AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - GREEN MANURES COVER CROPS WITH SMALLHOLDERS IN SOUTHEAST MEXICO, 1997-2001 (Box R3730)
    - RF 96047 #116 - SENDEROS Y ENCUENTROS PARA UN DESARROLLO AUTONOMO Y SUSTENTABLE (MEXICO) - TRAINING CENTER FOR TRAINERS AND FARMERS IN SIERRA SANTA MARTA, VERACRUZ, 1999-2001 (Box R3730)
    - RF 96048 #64 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - COUNTRY-LEVEL PROGRAMMING FOR ADOLESCENT HEALTH, 1997-2001 (Box R3730)
    - RF 96051 #123 - MAZINGIRA INSTITUTE (KENYA) - COMIC BOOK SERIES FOR MINDS ACROSS AFRICA SCHOOL CLUBS, 1997-2003 (Box R3730)
    - RF 96052 - AFRICAN FORUM ON CHILDREN'S TECHNOLOGICAL LITERACY, 1986-1997 (Box R3730)
- AC.2005.050: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2003; AC.2005.050; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3731.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC,2005,050,1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 96052 #77 - UNIVERSITY OF DURBAN-WESTVILLE (SOUTH AFRICA) - AFRICAN FORUM FOR CHILDREN'S LITERACY IN SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY, 1996-2002 (Box R3731)
    - RF 97001 #514 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - PLASTID ENGINEERING FOR RICE IMPROVEMENT, 1995-2003 (Box R3731)
    - RF 97001 #531 - INSTITUTE OF BIOTECHNOLOGY - NATIONAL CENTER FOR NATURAL SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY (VIETNAM) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR NGUYEN DUC THANH, 1997-2002 (Box R3731)
    - RF 97001 #538 - TRIBHUVAN UNIVERSITY - INSTITUTE OF AGRICULTURE AND ANIMAL RESEARCH (NEPAL) - RICE GERMPLASM AND MOLECULAR TECHNIQUES, 1997-2002 (Box R3731)
    - RF 97001 #541 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - MARKER-ASSISTED SELECTION AND DROUGHT RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1996-2002 (Box R3731)
    - RF 97001 #546 - UNIVERSITY OF MADRAS - FLUORESCENT PSEUDONOMADS, 1989-2002 (Box R3731)
- AC.2005.052: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2005.052; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3732, R3735, R3736.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.052.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 97016 #175 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - BC CONFERENCE: INTERNATIONAL EXHIBITIONS, 1997-2000 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97001 #602 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - RICE STRIPE AND VIRUSES RESISTANCE, 1990-2001 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97003 #17 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - INTROGRESSING FOR STRIGA HERMONTHICA IN MAIZE, 1997-2002 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97012 #129 - RAND CORP. - FERTILITY AND EDUCATION OF CHILDREN IN CAMEROON, 1997-2001 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97012 #143 - POPULATION REFERENCE BUREAU - COLLABORATION BETWEEN JAPANESE AND AMERICAN NGO'S, 1994-2001 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97012 #145 - (POPULATION SCIENCES) - BC CONFERENCE: GLOBAL FERTILITY TRANSITION, 1997-2000 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97021 #59 - CENTER FOR PALESTINE RESEARCH AND STUDIES (ISRAEL) - PROJECTS ON MODERN ISLAMIC POLITICS AND THOUGHT AND FOUR PUBLIC OPINION POLLS, 1996-2002 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97021 #61 - OBOR - ARAB WORLD OBOR AFFILIATE, 1994-2001 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97022 #274 - KERRIGAN, LODGE - FILM, "BLOOD IN THE WATER", 1998-2002 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97022 #293 - BROWN, TOM E. - "PUSHING DEAD", 1999-2002 (Box R3732)
    - RF 97026 #15 - (BUILDING COMMUNITY) - BC CONFERENCE: COMMUNITY BUILDING INTERNATIONAL, 1997-1998 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97026 #15 - (BUILDING COMMUNITY) - BC CONFERENCE: COMMUNITY BUILDING INTERNATIONAL - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1997-1998 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97031 #516 - LONDON SCHOOL OF ECONOMICS AND POLITICAL SCIENCE (ENGLAND) - BRIAN ABEL-SMITH READERSHIP OF HEALTH POLICY, 1997-2003 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97031 #520 - INCLEN, INC. - AFRICLEN PLANNING ACTIVITIES, 1999-2001 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97033 #67 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - INCLEN XVI GLOBAL MEETING IN THAILAND, 1998-1999 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97033 #75 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - 1999 PHSWOW NETWORK MEETING, 1999-2001 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #801 - ATIENO, ROSEMARY - ACA: RURAL INFRASTRUCTURE AND DEVELOPMENT OF PRIVATE TRADE IN KENYA'S AGRICULTURAL SECTOR, 1998-2002 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #814 - JEEBHAY, MOHAMED FAREED - ADIA: OCCUPATIONAL ALLERGY ASSOCIATED WITH FISH AND LOBSTER PROCESSING IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1999-2002 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #816 - BASHAASHA, BERNARD - ACA: IMPACT OF POPULATION AND LAND USE ON HOUSEHOLD WELFARE AND NATURAL RESOURCES IN UGANDA, 1998-2001 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #821 - NAIDOO, NITHISEELAN RAJEN - ADIA: "RESPIRATORY HEALTH AMONG SOUTH AFRICAN COAL MINERS", 1999-2004 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #823 - DIOP-SIDIBE, NAFISSATOU - ADIA: DOMESTIC VIOLENCE IN BAMAKO, MALI, 1999-2004 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #829 - OUEDRAOGO, CHRISTINE - ACA: HOW LOANS EMPOWER WOMEN IN BAZEGA, BURKINA FASO, 1998-2004 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #830 - RUKAZAMBUGA, NTIRUSHWA D.T. - ACA: RESEARCH ON BANANA WEEVIL IN BUKOBA, TANZANIA, 1996-2002 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #836 - AWUMA, KOSI SEMEBIA - ADIA: GRAZINGLANDS IN GHANA, 1999-2004 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #841 - KENDIE, STEPHEN BUGU - ACA: WATER SUPPLY IN NORTHERN GHANA, 1999-2002 (Box R3735)
    - RF 97034 #842 - OWINO, PIUS S. WASUNNA - ACA: SUSTAINABLE COMMUNITY PHARMACIES IN KENYA, 1998-2001 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97034 #847 - KEDERA, CHAGEMA JOHN - ACA: FUSARIUM PATHOGENS ASSOCIATED WITH MAIZE IN KENYA, 1999-2001 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97034 #851 - MAZAMBANI, DAVID - ACA: GOVERNANCE AND WELFARE OF RURAL WOMEN IN NYANGA, ZIMBABWE, 1998-2002 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97034 #856 - IKAMARI, LAWRENCE D.E. - ACA: MATERNAL HEALTH CARE IN TESO, KEYA, 1999-2001 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97042 #11 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - TRAINING IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR NORTH KOREAN SCIENTISTS, 1998-2003 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97042 #12 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - TRAINING IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR NORTH KOREAN SCIENTISTS, 1999-2002 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97042 #7 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - TRAINING FOR NORTH KOREAN SCIENTISTS IN NON-RADIOACTIVE PROTOCOLS AND NUCLEID ACID, 2000-2002 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97045 #71 - INCLEN, INC. - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH WORKING GROUP, 1992-2002 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97045 #71 - INCLEN, INC. - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH WORKING GROUP, 1992-2002 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97045 #77 - WESTERN CONSORTIUM FOR PUBLIC HEALTH - AFRICAN ADOLESCENT REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND SEXUALITY, 1993-2002 (Box R3736)
    - RF 97045 #78 - BURKINA FASO - HEALTH {MINISTRY OF) - INTERVENTION RESEARCH ON ADOLESCENT REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH (RESCINDED), 1999-2003 (Box R3736)
- AC.2005.060: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2004; AC.2005.060; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3737.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.060.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 97045 #94 - RESEARCH, ACTION AND INFORMATION NETWORK FOR THE BODILY INTEGRITY OF WOMEN - AFRICAN PARTNERSHI P FOR SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND RIGHTS OF WOMEN, 2000-2002 (Box R3737)
    - RF 97047 #128 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - MINDS ACROSS AFRICA SCHOOL CLUBS PROJECT, 1998-2004 (Box R3737)
    - RF 97047 #133 - WORLD BANK - MULTI-AGENCY PARTNERSHIP ON GIRLS' EDUCATION, 1998-2004 (Box R3737)
    - RF 97047 #135 - MALIAN ASSOCIATION FOR THE SUPPORT OF GIRLS' EDICATION - FAWE MALI CHAPTER, 1998-2003 (Box R3737)
    - RF 97047 #143 - FORUM FOR WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS - CHAD - GIRLS' CLUBS IN SCHOOLS IN CHAD, 1999-2001 (Box R3737)
    - RF 97047 #149 - AMOYE INSTITUTE FOR EDUCATIONAL RESEARH AND DEVELOPMENT (NIGERIA) - TEXBOOKS BY FEMALE AFRICAN AUTHORS FOR SECONDARY SCHOOLS, 1998-2004 (Box R3737)
    - RF 97047 #155 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS (KENYA) - FEMALE EDUCATION IN MATHEMATICS AND SCIENCE, 1995-2001 (Box R3737)
- AC.2005.069: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2003; AC.2005.069; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3738-R3740.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.069.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 97051 #8 - LIFE AND PEACE INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - ROLE OF ARGENTINE RELIGIOUS INSTITUTIONS IN TRANSITION TO DEMOCRACY, 1997-2002 (Box R3738)
    - RF 97051 #8 - LIFE AND PEACE INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - ROLE OF ARGENTINE RELIGIOUS INSTITUTIONS IN TRANSITION TO DEMOCRACY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1997-2002 (Box R3738)
    - RF 97057 #61 - SITKA TRIBE OF ALASKA - MULTl-MEDIA YOUTH PROJECT, 1999-2003 (Box R3738)
    - RF 97057 #64 - TAOS DAY SCHOOL - CORRAL RECONSTRUCTION PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3738)
    - RF 98001 #615 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - MAPPING RESISTANCE GENES TO YELLOW STEM BORER IN RICE, 1997-2001 (Box R3738)
    - RF 98001 #619 - UNIVERSITY OF COSTA RICA - RICE HOJA BLANCA VIRUS, 1990-2001 (Box R3728, Box R3729)
    - RF 98001 #627 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - MOLECULAR CHARACTERIZATION OF BACTERIAL BLIGHT AND BLAST, 1998-2001 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98001 #639 - TRIBHUVAN UNIVERSITY (NEPAL) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR RAM C. SHARMA, 1998-2002 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98001 #642 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - AGRONOMIC GENES AND WILD TO CULTIVATED RICE, 1998-2003 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98001 #643 - MALAYSIAN AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE - PATHOGEN DERIVED RESISTANCE IN RICE TUNGRO DISEASE, 1997-2002 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98001 #646 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - RICE RAGGED STUNT VIRUS, 1991-2003 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98001 #652 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - INDICA/JAPONICA RICE GENOMES, 1998-2003 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98001 #653 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - NEAR-ISOGENIC INTROGRESSION LINES AND INDICA/JAPONICA RICE GENOMES, 1998-2003 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98001 #654 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR K. R. RAJYASHRI, 1997-2001 (Box R3739)
    - RF 98008 #12 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - BIOLOGICAL MANAGEMENT OF WATER HYACINTH WASTES FROM LAKE VICTORIA, 1998-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #660 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY COLLABORATIVE RESEARCH WITH MONSANTO COMPANY, 1998-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #670 - ACADEMIA SINICA (CHINA) - TAGGING GENETIC MALE STERILE GENES IN RICE, 1992-2001 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #673 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - IMPROVEMENT OF THAI RICE FOR ABIOTIC STRESS TOLERANCE, 1998-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #674 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - SALT TOLERANCE IN RICE, 1995-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #677 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - RHIZOCTONIA TOXIN-IN-ACTIVATING GENES AND RICE, 1994-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #678 - MADURAI KAMARAJ UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF INDICA RICE FOR DROUGHT AND SALINITY TOLERANCE, 1998-2001 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #694 - GYEONGSANG NATIONAL UNIVERSITY (NORTH KOREA) - IDENTIFY AND ISOLATE RICE GENES, 1997-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98001 #703 - SPIC SCIENCE FOUNDATION (INDIA) - DEVELOPMENT OF TRANSPOSON TRAP LINES IN RICE, 1998-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98007 #44 - SSEBULIBA, RUTH N. - TRAINING IN BANANA BREEDING, 1999-2001 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98009 #11 - MUREITHI, JOSEPH G. - CAREER DEVELOPMENT FELLOWSHIP, 1996-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98009 #13 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - SMALLHOLDER SOYABEAN/MAIZE PRODUCTION TECHNOLOGIES AND RURAL FOOD SECURITY, 1999-2002 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98012 #19 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - WORKSHOP ON TRANSGENIC RICE RESISTANCE TO RICE HOJA BLANCA VIRUS, 1999-2000 (Box R3740)
    - RF 98013 #171 - (POPULATION SCIENCES) - BC CONFERENCE: SYMPOSIUM ON POPULATION CHANGE AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1998-2001 (Box R3740)
- AC.2005.072: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2005; AC.2005.072; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3741, R3751-R3755.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.072.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 98013 #172 - CENTER FOR CULTURAL AND TECHNICAL INTERCHANGE BETWEEN EAST AND WEST - CAIRO PLUS 5 MEETING OF NGOS, 1998-2002 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98013 #176 - SAVE THE CHILDREN - CAIRO PLUS 5 WORK WITH EUROPEAN AGENCIES, 1998-2002 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98013 #180 - SENEGAL - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - QUALITY OF SERVICE AND FAMILY PLANNING, 1998-2001 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98013 #181 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - PANEL ON AGING, 1998-2003 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98013 #181 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - PANEL ON AGING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2003 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98020 #30 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - JOB QUALITY AND MOBILITY OPPORTUNITIES FOR CUSTOMER SERVICE AND SALES WORKERS, 1998-2001 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98020 #31 - BOWDOIN COLLEGE - CHANGES IN EMPLOYMENT PRACTICE IN HOSIERY INDUSTRY, 1999-2001 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98023 - INITIATIVES FOR EQUITY IN HEALTH, 1998-2000 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98023 #32 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - SPANISH TRANSLATION OF GLOBAL HEALTH EQUITY INITIATIVE VOLUME, 1999-2004 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98023 #36 - LAOS - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - DISEASE SURVEILLANCE NETWORK, 1999-2002 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98023 #38 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - HEALTH CARE IN COUNTRIES RECEIVING DEBT RELIEF, 1999-2001 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98023 #46 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF PREVENTIVE MEDICINE - 9TH INTERNATIONAL WFPHA CONGRESS, 1999-2001 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98024 #88 - TALWAR RESEARCH FOUNDATION (INDIA) - HCG ANTIBODIES FOR EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION, 1998-2002 (Box R3741)
    - RF 98024 #89 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL (ENGLAND) - MICROBICIDE STUDY IN THE MACAQUE, 1998-2001 (Box R3741)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RESIDENT (Al Musawi, Muhsin), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Alting von Geusau, Frans A.), 1997-2002 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Andreo, Carlos Santiago), 1998-2000 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Arens, William), 1998-2002 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Arian, Asher), 1997-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Aspin, David) (CO-RESIDENT: Chapman, Judith D.), 1997-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Atkin, J. Myron) (CO-RESIDENT: Black, Paul J.), 1998-2003 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Bagg, Robert Ely), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Bair, Deidre), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Bambach, Carmen C.), 1999-2000 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Bender, Carl M.) (CO-RESIDENT: Jones, Hugh F.), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Blanc, Paul D.), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Boinchan, Boris P.), 1997-2000 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Bourque, Susan C.) (CO-RESIDENT: Navarro, Marysa), 1997-2000 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Brackenridge, J. Bruce), 1998-2003 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Braginskaia, Nina V.) (CO-RESIDENT: Sorokina, Marina Yu), 1999-2000 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Briscoe, John), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Brown, Valerie Anne), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Burshtein, Anatoly), 1998-2001 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Canemaker, John), 1998-2004 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Chlibec, Jan), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Clark, Stuart), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Clemens, Elisabeth S.), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Cofer, Judith Ortiz), 1998-1999 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Cook, Rebecca) (CO-RESIDENT: Dickens, Bernard), 1998-2003 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Cooper, Catherine R.), 1999-2000 (Box R3751)
    - RESIDENT (Corson, David J.), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Crane, Diana), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Cunningham, Kevin), 1999-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Davis, Anne J.) (CO-RESIDENT: Mitoh, Takako), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Davison, Peter), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Debas, Haile Tesfaye), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (DeFrantz, Thomas), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Derdyk, Edith), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Dominguez, Jorgei Ignacio) (CO-RESIDENT: Fernandez de Castro, Rafael), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Dowling, John E.), 1998-2005 (Box R3752)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2026
    - RESIDENT (Eckert, Penelope D.) (CO-RESIDENT: McConnell-Ginet, Sally), 1998-2003 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Edelman, Marian Wright), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Elver, Hilal) (CO-RESIDENT: Falk, Richard A.), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Escobar, Arturo) (CO-RESIDENT: Leff, Enrique), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Fennelly, Brian), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Fiske, Ingrid Jean), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Freed, Donald), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Garcia, Orlando Jacinto), 1998-2001 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Greenberg, Alvin), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Greenblatt, Stephen), 1998-2001 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Harnish, Robert M.), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Hayles, N. Katherine), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Healey, Michael Charles) (CO-RESIDENT: Hennessey, Timothy M.), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Hendrix, Jan), 1998-2000 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Ireland, Patrick R.), 1998-2004 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT (Jesurun, John), 1998-1999 (Box R3752)
    - RESIDENT {Johansen, Baber), 1998-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Jussawalla, Feroza Framji), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Kakar, Sudhir), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Kane, Ousmane), 1999-2003 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Keller, Morton) (CO-RESIDENT: Keller, Phyllis), 1998-2001 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Kidder, Tracy), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Kingston, Maxine Hong), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Kobbekaduwa, Leela A.), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Kulin, Howard E.), 1998-2001 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Kurka Piotr), 1999-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Landes, David S.), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Lefcourt, Herbert Michael), 1998-2001 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Legg, James), 1998-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Levtzion, Nehemia), 1997-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Lichtenstein, Nelson), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Liebermann, Lowell), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Lipking, Lawrence), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Lister, Ardele Diane), 1998-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Lockwood, Annea F.), 1998-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Loescher, Gilburt), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Lumelsky, Vladimir J.), 1998-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Luorong, Zhandui), 1997-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Marcus, George E.), 1997-2002 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Martin, Richard Peter), 1998-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Maynard, Nancy Hicks), 1998-2000 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Mee, Charles L.), 1998-1999 (Box R3753)
    - RESIDENT (Metcalf, Barbara D.), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)